Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Assistant Files, 1965-2011; III.
  - Ken Altman, 1997-2010; 1.
    - Higher education, 2009-2010 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Higher education legislation, 1997-2007 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Higher education legislation, 2009 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - Higher education legislation, 2010 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Housing, 2004-2010 (Box 332, Folder 12-14)
    - Housing crisis hearing, 2010 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Lobbying, 2006 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Lobbying, 2008 (Box 333, Folder 3-4)
    - Memos, 2008 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 2009 (Box 333, Folder 6-8)
    - Miscellaneous office paperwork, 2009 (Box 333, Folder 9-10)
    - Miscellaneous topics, 2003-2009 (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - New Urban Agenda Act, 2001 (Box 333, Folder 12-13)
    - Omnibus Conference, 2009 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia Housing Authority, 2007-2009 (Box 333, Folder 15)
    - Philadelphia Housing Authority, 2007-2009 (Box 334, Folder 1-3)
    - Phildelphia Housing Authority, Moving to work, 2006-2008 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Subcommittee on Commerce, Justice, and Science, 2009 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Surveys, 2004 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Stimulus, 2009 (Box 334, Folder 7-9)
  - Adrienne Baker, 1988-2010; 2.
    Adrienne Baker served as: legislative assistant (education, energy, environment, housing, urban affairs, welfare), 1999-2002; and executive director, 2003-2010.
    - Army Corp of Engineers, Route 222 bypass, 2001-2003 (Box 334, Folder 10-11)
    - Clean Air Act, 2001 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Clean Air Act, Background, 1997 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Clean Air Act, Chafee letter, 1990-1996 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Clean Air Act, D'Amato and Ridge, 1997 (Box 334, Folder 15)
    - Clean Air Act, EPA materials, 1993-1998 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Clean Air Act, Guides, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Clean Air Act, Inhofe bill, 1997-1998 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Clean Air Act, Letters and memos, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Clean Air Act, Ozone transport, 1994-1996 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Clean Air Act, Pennsylvania clean air and global warming, 1999 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Clean Air Act, Pittsburgh attainment, 1996 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Clean Air Act, Polls and opposition, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Clean Air Act, Support, 1996-1997 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Constitution Heritage Act, 1988 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Environment, Council on Superconductivity, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Enviroment, Events and meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Environment, Legislation, 1998-2000 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Environment, Letters, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Environment, Local, 1997-2000 (Box 335, Folder 15)
    - Environment, Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 335, Folder 16)
    - Environment, Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 17)
    - Environment, Sierra Club endorsement, 1990-1992 (Box 335, Folder 18)
    - Environment, Vehicle emissions, 1996-1997 (Box 335, Folder 19)
    - Environment, Virginia accelerator, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 20)
    - Historical and museum updates, 1992-1997 (Box 335, Folder 21)
    - Housing, Budget requests, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 22)
    - Housing, Constituent affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 23)
    - Housing, Hazelton and Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 335, Folder 24)
    - Housing, Legislation, 1997-1999 (Box 335, Folder 25)
    - Housing, Multifamily, 2000 (Box 335, Folder 26)
    - Housing, Organizations, 1999-2001 (Box 335, Folder 27)
    - Housing, Pennsylvania flood damage, 1996 (Box 335, Folder 28)
    - Housing, Philidelphia Housing Authority, 1999-2000 (Box 335, Folder 29)
    - Housing, Pittsburgh Housing Authority, 2001 (Box 335, Folder 30)
    - Housing, Pittsburgh low-income housing, 1996 (Box 335, Folder 31)
    - Housing, Sanders Decree, 1999 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Housing, Sanders Decree clips, 1999 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Housing, Sanders Decree letters, 1999 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Housing, State-level, 1998-2000 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Housing, Tamaqua, 1995-1996 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Housing, Ten-year warrentee, 1999 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Urban Development, 1995-1997 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Interior requests, 1994-2000 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - New Urban Agenda, 1989 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Mel Martinez, 2001 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Safe Drinking Water Act, 1994 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Trips, October-December 2001 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - Trips, March-May 2002 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - Trips, July-October 2002 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - Trips, November 5, 2002 (Box 336, Folder 16)
    - Trips, November 26, 2002 (Box 336, Folder 17)
    - Trips, November 26, 2002 (Box 336, Folder 18)
    - Trips, November 26, 2002 (Box 336, Folder 19)
    - Trips, May-July 2003 (Box 336, Folder 20)
    - Trips, August 2003 (Box 336, Folder 21)
    - Trips, October 2003 (Box 336, Folder 22)
    - Trips, December 2003 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Trips, February-April 2004 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Trips, June-September 2004 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Trips, October-December 2004 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Trips, 2006 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Trips, March-April 2007 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Trips, May-November 2007 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Trips, January-September 2008 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Trips, October-December 2008 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Trips, February-May 2009 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Trips, June-August 2009 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Trips, September 2009-March 2010 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Trips, Expense reports, undated (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Urban aid, 1995 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Urban Agenda Bill, 1997 (Box 337, Folder 15)
  - Michael Blume, 1965-1992; 3.
    Michael Bloom served as: legislative correspondent, 1990-1991; and legislative aide, 1992.
    - Armenian genocide, 1989 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - Armenian genocide, 1989-1990 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - Armenian genocide, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 1-2)
    - Armenian genocide, Armenian Assembly of America, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Armenian genocide, Assembly of Turkish American Associations, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Armenian genocide, Aydin Corporation correspondence, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Armenian genocide, Congressional Records, 1986-1989 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Armenian genocide, Contacts, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Armenian genocide, Form letter drafts for response to Res. 212, 1989-1990 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Armenian genocide, Letters and memos, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Armenian genocide, Mid-Atlantic Research Associates newsletter, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Armenian genocide, Newsclips, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Armenian genocide, Ozbekhan correspondence, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Armenian genocide, Pamphlets and booklets, 1965-1985 (Box 338, Folder 13)
    - Armenian genocide, Quincentennial Foundation of Instanbul, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Armenian genocide, Schnader, Harrison, Segal & Lewis correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 338, Folder 15)
    - Armenian genocide, Senate and background information, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 16)
    - Armenian genocide, Turkish Embassy files, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 17)
    - Campaign, Debate prep, October 1992 (Box 338, Folder 18)
    - Campaign, Defense for Yeakel, 1991-1992 (Box 338, Folder 19)
    - Campaign, Memos, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 20)
    - Campaign, Notch babies, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 21)
    - Campaign, Ross Perot, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 22)
    - Campaign, Yeakel paralegals speech, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 23)
    - Citizen Jury Pittsburgh, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 24)
    - Civil rights, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 25)
    - Conservative highlights, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 26)
    - Crime, undated (Box 338, Folder 27)
    - Economic development, undated (Box 338, Folder 28)
    - Employer-employee relations, Jobs and healthcare, undated (Box 338, Folder 29)
    - Energy, Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1986-1990 (Box 338, Folder 30)
    - Energy, Corporate Average Fuel Economy, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 31)
    - Energy, Clean Air Act, undated (Box 338, Folder 32)
    - Energy, Conservation, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 33)
    - Energy, Environment and energy conservation, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 34)
    - Energy, National Energy Strategy, 1990-1991 (Box 338, Folder 35)
    - Energy, Public transportation, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 36)
    - Energy, Weatherization, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 37)
    - Flag burning, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 38)
    - Foreign policy, Eastern Europe background and notes, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 39)
    - Foreign policy, Eastern Europe floor statements, 1989-1990 (Box 338, Folder 40)
    - Foreign policy, Eastern Europe newsclips, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 41)
    - Foreign policy, Eastern Europe voting record, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 42)
    - Foreign policy, Europe/NATO in Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 338, Folder 43)
    - Foreign policy, Israel background and notes, undated (Box 338, Folder 44)
    - Foreign policy, Israel floor statements, 1988-1990 (Box 338, Folder 45)
    - Foreign policy, Israel newsclips, 1988-1990 (Box 338, Folder 46)
    - Foreign policy, Israel voting record, 1987-1990 (Box 338, Folder 47)
    - Jobs and labor, 1991 (Box 338, Folder 48)
    - Major accomplishments, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 49)
    - Manufacturing, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 50)
    - Bob McCarson, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 51)
    - Minority and female judges in Pennsylvania, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 52)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 53)
    - Norfolk land conveyance, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 54)
    - Professional sports leagues and antitrust matters, 1987-1991 (Box 338, Folder 55)
    - Released to press, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Ann Richards, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - School choice, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Selected favorable statements by other senators, 1989-1992 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Seniority benefits, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Serwach articles, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Statistics, Moderate record for Specter, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Statistics, Northwest-Midwest Congressional Coalition, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Statistics, Party unity, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Statistics, Public laws by Specter, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Statistics, Selected Philidelphia accomplishments, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Statistics, Senate overridden veto votes, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - Statistics, Senate sustained veto votes, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 14)
    - Statistics, Seniority numbers in the Senate, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - Statistics, Votes against women's groups, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 16)
    - Statistics, Votes for tax increases, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 17)
    - Statistics, Western Pennslyvania infrastructure, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 18)
    - Women, FreInd, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 19)
  - Chris Bradish, 1990-2010; 4.
    Chris Bradish served as: staff assistant, 2002-2003; legislative correspondent, 2004-2005; legislative assistant, 2006-2009; and director, 2010.
    - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 339, Folder 20)
    - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 339, Folder 21-22)
    - Approprations, Thanks, 1999 (Box 339, Folder 23)
    - Cloning, 1995-1998 (Box 339, Folder 24-26)
    - Constituent mail, 1997-2002 (Box 339, Folder 27-28)
    - Defense, A-76, 2002 (Box 339, Folder 29)
    - Defense, AgraCo, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 30)
    - Defense, AirCrane, 2001 (Box 339, Folder 31)
    - Defense, Altoona Hospital, 2001 (Box 339, Folder 32)
    - Defense, American Robot, 2001 (Box 339, Folder 33)
    - Defense, American victims of terrorism, 2000-2001 (Box 339, Folder 34-36)
    - Defense, Anthrax, 2002 (Box 339, Folder 37)
    - Defense, Anthrax vaccine, 2001 (Box 339, Folder 38)
    - Defense, Appropriation program lists, 2001-2002 (Box 339, Folder 39)
    - Defense, Appropriations, 2001 (Box 340, Folder 1-3)
    - Defense, Appropriations, 2002 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Appropriations, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 5-8)
    - Defense, Appropriations correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Defense, Approprations requests, 2001-2003 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Defense, Army Black Beret, 2000 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Armor project, 2005 (Box 340, Folder 12-16)
    - Defense, Army Heritage Center, 2001-2004 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Atmospheric Interceptor Technology, 2001 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Defense, BAC Systems, 2000 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Ballistic missiles, 1999 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Defense, BRAC, 1995 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Defense, BRAC, 2002-2004 (Box 341, Folder 6-8)
    - Defense, BRAC, 2005 (Box 341, Folder 9-13)
    - Defense, BRAC, 911th Airlift Wing, 2004-2005 (Box 341, Folder 14-15)
    - Defense, BRAC, Letterkenny, 2003-2008 (Box 341, Folder 16)
    - Defense, BRAC, Letterkenny, 2003-2008 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Defense, BRAC, Pennsylvania impact, 2005 (Box 342, Folder 2-7)
    - Defense, BRAC, Tobyhanna, 1997-2004 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Defense, BRAC, Willow Grove, 2005 (Box 342, Folder 9-13)
    - Defense, BRAC, Willow Grove, 2007-2008 (Box 342, Folder 14-15)
    - Defense, Boeing, 1999-2002 (Box 342, Folder 16)
    - Defense, British defense, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Buy American requirements, 1998 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Defense, Combatting Terrorism, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Contractors, 1999-2002 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Department of Defense, Ovarian cancer research, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Defense, Depot caucus, 2003-2004 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Defense, Dielectrokinetic Laboratories, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Defense, EDO Corporation, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Defense, FastShip, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Defense, Flight 93, 2002 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - Defense, Flight 93 bill, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Floor statements on terrorism, 1981-2002 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Defense, General Electric, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Gettysburg Museum, 2002 (Box 343, Folder 14)
    - Defense, Harris, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 15)
    - Defense, Homeland Security, 2001-2002 (Box 343, Folder 16)
    - Defense, Intelligence, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 17)
    - Defense, Iraq, Binder 1, 2006-2007 (Box 343, Folder 18)
    - Defense, Iraq, Binder 2 (Box 343, Folder 19)
    - Defense, Iraq, Binder 3, 2006-2007 (Box 343, Folder 20-23)
    - Defense, Kvaerner Shipyard, 1998-2001 (Box 343, Folder 24)
    - Defense, Lancaster Composite, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Letterkenny Army Depot, 1993-2000 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Defense, Mechanicsburg, 1999 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Megacenter downsizing, 1998 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Military alcohol research, 2000 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Defense, Military construction, 2001-2003 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Defense, NABCO, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Defense, National Defense Industrial Association, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Defense, National Guard, 2001-2004 (Box 344, Folder 9-10)
    - Defense, National Missile Defense, 1990-2002 (Box 344, Folder 11-12)
    - Defense, NAVAIR, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Naval Supply Systems, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 14)
    - Defense, Navy Marine Intranet, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 15)
    - Defense, Northrop Grumman, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 16)
    - Defense, Pennsylvania Air National Guard, 2005 (Box 344, Folder 17)
    - Defense, Pennsyvania National Guard, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 18)
    - Defense, Philidelphia Navy Yard, 2004-2005 (Box 344, Folder 19-20)
    - Defense, Reserve Officers Association, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 21)
    - Defense, Scitefair, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 22)
    - Defense, Sea Cadets, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 23)
    - Defense, Service Acadamies, 2002-2003 (Box 344, Folder 24)
    - Defense, Stryker Brigade Combat Team, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 25)
    - Defense, Submarines, 2002 (Box 344, Folder 26)
    - Defense, Technicians, 2001 (Box 344, Folder 27)
    - Defense, Terrorism, 1997-2001 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Terrorism, 1999-2002 (Box 345, Folder 2-3)
    - Defense, United States Investigations Services, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Defense, USS J. William Ditter recognition, 2000 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Defense, V-22 Osprey, 1990-1992 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Defense, V-22 Osprey, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - Defense, Vectored Thrust Ducted Propeller Compound Helicopter, 2002 (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - Defense, Veterans History Project, 2002 (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - Defense, VIP mail, 1994-2001 (Box 345, Folder 10-11)
    - Defense, Weapons proliferation charts (Box 345, Folder 12)
    - Defense, World Vision, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Washington Square Park, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 14)
    - Defense, XM-777 lightweight 155mm howitzer, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 15)
    - Foreign affairs, 1999-2003 (Box 345, Folder 16)
    - Foreign affairs, Afghan women, 2002 (Box 345, Folder 17)
    - Foreign affiars, Belgrade, 1998 (Box 345, Folder 18)
    - Foreign affairs, Bosnia, 1997 (Box 345, Folder 19)
    - Foreign affairs, Bulgaria, 2002 (Box 345, Folder 20)
    - Foreign affiars, Central and South America, 2002 (Box 345, Folder 21)
    - Foreign affairs, China, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 22)
    - Foreign affairs, Cuba, 2001 (Box 345, Folder 23)
    - Foreign affairs, Darfur, 2006 (Box 345, Folder 24-26)
    - Foreign affairs, Egypt, 1997-1998 (Box 345, Folder 27)
    - Foreign affairs, Egypt, 2001-2002 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Foreign affairs, Eritrea, 1998 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Foreign affairs, Ethiopia, 1998 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Foreign affairs, Foreign Operations appropriations, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Foreign affairs, Foreign trips, 2000-2003 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Foreign affairs, Germany, 1998 (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Foreign affairs, The Hague, 1997-1998 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Foreign affairs, Halt Funding to Palestinian Authority, 1997-2001 (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Foreign affairs, International Religious Freedom Act, 2001 (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Foreign affairs, International Visitors Council, 2001-2002 (Box 346, Folder 10)
    - Foreign affairs, Iran, 2000 (Box 346, Folder 11-12)
    - Foreign affairs, Iran, 2006 (Box 346, Folder 13-14)
    - Foreign affairs, Iran Project, 2006 (Box 346, Folder 15-20)
    - Foreign affairs, Iran Project, 2006 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Foreign affairs, Iraq, 2001-2002 (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Foreign affairs, Israel, 1997-2001 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Foreign affairs, Israeli-Palestinian conflict, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 4-5)
    - Foreign affairs, Italy, 1997-1998 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Foreign affairs, Jews in Iran, 1999 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Foreign affairs, Jordan, 1998 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - Foreign affairs, Kuwait accident, 2001 (Box 347, Folder 9)
    - Foreign affairs, Law of the Sea Convention, 2004 (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - Foreign affairs, Wen Ho Lee, 2000 (Box 347, Folder 11)
    - Foreign affairs, Peru, 2001-2002 (Box 347, Folder 12)
    - Foreign affairs, Poland, 2002 (Box 347, Folder 13)
    - Foreign affairs, Romania, 2002 (Box 347, Folder 14)
    - Foreign affairs, Russia, 2001 (Box 347, Folder 15)
    - Foreign affairs, Saudi Arabia, 1998 (Box 347, Folder 16)
    - Foreign affairs, Saudi Arabia, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 17)
    - Foreign affairs, Saudi Arabia, 2004-2006 (Box 347, Folder 18-21)
    - Foreign affairs, Senate proceedings, 2004-2006 (Box 347, Folder 22)
    - Foreign affairs, Supporting Human Rights and Democracy, 2003-2004 (Box 347, Folder 23)
    - Foreign affairs, Syria, 1998 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Foreign affairs, Syria, 2006 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Foreign affairs, Thailand, 2001 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Foreign affairs, United Nations trip, 2006 (Box 348, Folder 4-6)
    - Foreign affairs, United States citizens in Israel, 1999 (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - Foreign affairs, United States Institute of Peace, 2002 (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - Foreign affairs, Vaccines, 2000 (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Foreign affairs, VIP mail, 1996-2001 (Box 348, Folder 10-12)
    - Foreign affairs, War crimes tribunals, 2001-2002 (Box 348, Folder 13)
    - Foreign affairs, Yemen, 1998 (Box 348, Folder 14)
    - Intelligence, 2002 (Box 348, Folder 15-18)
    - Judiciary Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 348, Folder 19)
    - Judiciary Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Letters and memos, 2002-2003 (Box 349, Folder 2-3)
    - Memos, 2006 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Philadephia VA Medical Center, 2009-2010 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Ray Communications, 1998-2002 (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - School of the Americas, 1997-2000 (Box 349, Folder 7-9)
    - Specter accomplishments, 1997 (Box 349, Folder 10)
    - Leon Sullivan, 1999-2001 (Box 349, Folder 11)
    - Trade, 2001 (Box 349, Folder 12)
    - Trade, 2001-2002 (Box 349, Folder 13)
    - Trade, 2006-2007 (Box 349, Folder 14)
    - Trade, Adjustment assistance, 2002 (Box 349, Folder 15)
    - Trade, Air Products and Chemical, 2001 (Box 349, Folder 16)
    - Trade, Antitrust, 1996 (Box 349, Folder 17)
    - Trade, Africa Summit, 2001 (Box 349, Folder 18)
    - Trade, Africa Trade Bill, 1999 (Box 349, Folder 19-20)
    - Trade, African Growth and Opportunity Act, Caribbean Basin Initiative, 2000 (Box 349, Folder 21)
    - Trade, American Chamber of Commerce in Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 349, Folder 22)
    - Trade, Andean trade, 2001-2002 (Box 350, Folder 1-2)
    - Trade, Apples, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Trade, Armstrong World Industies, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Trade, Asian trade, 1994-1998 (Box 350, Folder 5-6)
    - Trade, Australia, 2004 (Box 350, Folder 7)
    - Trade, Bananas, 1999 (Box 350, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Beef imports, 1999 (Box 350, Folder 9)
    - Trade, Boeing, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 10)
    - Trade, Bonney Forge, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 11)
    - Trade, Brockway Glass, 2000-2001 (Box 350, Folder 12)
    - Trade Caucus for Farmers and Ranchers, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 13)
    - Trade, Cell Pathways, 2000 (Box 350, Folder 14)
    - Trade, Chilean grapes, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 15)
    - Trade, China trade agreement, 1999 (Box 350, Folder 16)
    - Trade, Chinese trade, 1997 (Box 350, Folder 17)
    - Trade, Commerce, Justice and State appropriations, 2003 (Box 350, Folder 18)
    - Trade, Dana Corporation, 2000 (Box 350, Folder 19)
    - Trade, Department of the Treasury, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 20)
    - Trade, Dutch Gold Honey, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 21)
    - Trade, EGM Marine, 1999 (Box 350, Folder 22)
    - Trade, Export Administration Act, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 23-24)
    - Trade, Foreign steel, 1999-2000 (Box 350, Folder 25-26)
    - Trade, Foreign Trade Zone, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 27)
    - Trade, General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT), 1991-1997 (Box 350, Folder 28)
    - Trade, Glatfelter, 2000-2001 (Box 350, Folder 29)
    - Trade, Heinz-Vlasic merger, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 30)
    - Trade, International steel trade, 2001 (Box 350, Folder 31-32)
    - Trade, International steel trade, 2001 (Box 351, Folder 1-3)
    - Trade, Issues, 1995-1996 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - Trade, Issues, 1995-1999 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - Trade, Issues, 1998 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Trade, Japanese poultry trade, 2002 (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - Trade, Jordan free trade, 2001 (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Lamb, 2001 (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - Trade, Nuclear fuel, 2000 (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - Trade, Milk Protein Concentrate, 2001 (Box 351, Folder 11)
    - Trade, Pension bills, 2000 (Box 351, Folder 12)
    - Trade, Softwood lumbers, 2000-2001 (Box 351, Folder 13)
    - Trade, Sony, 2001-2004 (Box 351, Folder 14)
    - Trade, Sunoco, undated (Box 351, Folder 15)